The anterior epithelium, here, which will become
ここにある前部上皮は、やがて
a part, here, which is called the cornea, there, you see,
ここで角膜と呼ばれる一部となります。ほら、見てください、
the corneal epithelium, which is therefore a mesenchymal tissue,
角膜上皮は、間葉組織であり、
whereas the conjunctival tissue, we could say it is an
一方、結膜組織は
epithelial, thus a limiting tissue.
上皮性、つまり境界の組織です。
Then we have what is called the anterior chamber, the
次に、いわゆる前眼房、
pupillary orifice.
瞳孔があります。
You have three major tunics that surround the eye.
眼球を取り囲む3つの主要な膜があります。
So it's as if they were three socks, one inside the other.
ですから、それはまるで3枚の靴下が互いに入れ子になっているかのようです。
The first sock is called the sclera.
最初の膜は強膜と呼ばれます。
It is continuous with the cornea anteriorly.
それは前方の角膜と連続しています。
transparent, then you have the
透明で、次に
limbus, then the white part.
輪部があり、次に白い部分があります。
This is the first
これが最初の
layer. I remove this first
層です。この最初の層を取り除くと、
sock, and then, we encounter
膜を取り除くと、現れるのは
an important layer called the choroid.
脈絡膜と呼ばれる重要な層です。
And the choroid,
そして脈絡膜は、
we see here, you see,
ここで見られるように、ほら、
which is a layer that is
それは
extremely vascularized.
非常に血管に富んだ層です。
And this choroid continues
そしてこの脈絡膜は、
anteriorly, here,
ここで前方に
with what is called
いわゆる
the iris.
虹彩へと続いています。
Iridology is a reading of the mesodermal
虹彩診断学とは、中胚葉系の
vascular system.
血管系の読み取りです。
By observing the eye, you can see information about trophic changes
眼球を観察することで、栄養変化の情報を
of a vascular nature.
血管型で読み取ることができます。
This is expressed in the iris, which are sensors where they can store, for example,
それは虹彩に現れます。虹彩は、例えば情報を蓄積できるセンサーであり、
of sulfur.
硫黄の。
We can store a lot of things.
多くのものを貯蔵できます。
And we can learn to read. There is a mapping of how it will be arranged.
そして、私たちは読み方を学ぶことができます。それがどのように配置されるかのマッピングがあります。
there will be another relationship that will be
別の関係性が存在します。それは、
important, which is the ciliary processes
重要なもので、毛様体突起です。
and then there will be a relationship
そして、関係性が存在します。
with what we call the suspensory
いわゆる筋肉との。
muscles of the iris, which we will see in detail
虹彩懸垂筋です。これについては詳細に見ていきます。
later to understand their
後ほど、それらの
physiology.
生理学を理解するために。
So we see the crystalline lens,
したがって、水晶体が見えます。
the different chambers
様々な房が
that will appear, the pupillary orifice,
現れ、瞳孔口が。
Here, a little further,
ここに少し先に、
in this choroid
この脈絡膜の中に、
with the iris, you see.
虹彩と共に、ご覧の通りです。
which will form an important link with what is called the suspensory
いわゆる靭帯と重要な結合を形成します。
ligament.
懸垂靭帯です。
There is also a ciliary muscle; there is an accommodation system that will
毛様体筋も存在し、調節システムが
occur.
働きます。
Well, this accommodation system involves this lens, which we call the crystalline lens,
この調節システムとは、水晶体と呼ばれるこのレンズのことで、
by the ciliary muscles, with the ora serrata; well, we'll see that
毛様体筋によって、鋸状縁と共に、まあ、それは
later,
後で見ていきますが、
which will increase, change the shape
それが形状を増大させ、変化させます。
of my lens slightly, to allow the image to integrate
私のレンズをほんの少し、画像が適切に統合されるようにするために、
correctly on the retinal plane.
網膜平面上に。
First layer, the sclera.
最初の層、強膜。
Second layer, the choroid.
第二の層、脈絡膜。
Third layer, the retina.
第三の層、網膜。
The nervous tissue, the deepest, which is truly the expression of the brain.
最も深い神経組織で、真に脳の表現です。
With the colobomatous cleft, which gives rise to the anomaly.
コロボーマ性欠損を伴い、それが血管の経路を与える。
for the hyaloid artery and vessels
動脈と硝子体血管のために
which will form the retinal vessels, etc.
それが網膜血管などを形成します。
Colobomatous cleft, do you understand what it was?
コロボーマ裂、それが何であったか理解できましたか？
With, you see, this remnant here, then this closure that will occur.
ほら、ここにあるこの痕跡と、これから起こる閉鎖を伴って。
So the retina, in fact, is the innermost layer of the eye.
さて、網膜とは、実際には眼の最内層です。
And so, where does this retina come from?
では、この網膜はどこから来るのでしょうか？
Do you remember this first vesicle?
この最初の小胞を覚えていますか？
this small sphere that emerges, which we call the primary optic vesicle,
出てくるこの小さな球、第一次眼胞と呼ばれるものです。
which will make a movement like this, you see, like a
それがこのように動くでしょう、ほら、まるで
calyx, a cup.
杯、あるいは花瓶のように。
It is made of two layers, like this, you see, an inner layer, an outer layer.
それはこのように2つの層でできています、ほら、内層と外層です。
And this is where you understand what is called a retinal detachment.
そして、ここで網膜剥離と呼ばれるものが理解できるでしょう。
We can clearly see these two layers.
これらの2つの層がよく見えます。
Well, when people have a retinal detachment,
さて、人々が網膜剥離を起こすとき、
it is this layer that expands, it is this space between the inner leaflet
それはその層が剥がれることであり、網膜の内層と
and the outer leaflet of the retina.
網膜の外層の間です。
There will be another very thin layer here, which will be very important later, it is
ここにはさらに非常に薄い層があり、後で非常に重要になります。それは
what is called the pigmentary layer.
色素層と呼ばれるものです。
You will discuss this, I think, in detail tomorrow, it is the entire layer of this retina with
あなたは明日、これを詳細に話すでしょう、この網膜の全層と
the pigmentary layer,
色素層、
and then what are called the photoreceptors, which are of the type that you...
そして、光受容器と呼ばれるもの、それはあなたが知っている種類のものです...
know as cones and rods. But you also have a layer called
錐体と桿体として知っているものです。しかし、さらに別の層があります。それは
the ganglion cells. It is truly an important layer for
神経節細胞です。これは本当に重要な層であり、
information transfer
情報伝達の
to enable transduction. It is the conversion of a photon into electrical energy.
変換を与えるためです。それは光子がエネルギーに変換されることです。
electrical. Change
電気的。変化
members to sea.
膜の変化。